haha
but I'll have to explain this to you
and maybe you don't understand
no problem
because even I didn't understand
I put my hand on that steering wheel
tava with the mass feeling
but something told me it wasn't
that excitement I was having at the time
turned into a doubt you know
gave something to my head that made me see
the clearest things
and that's when I understood everything
all good
I wasn't looking for a business
actually
I was looking for an excuse
an excuse for me not to assume what I already knew
old
the truth is that I always knew what my business was
but i didn't want to accept
not for me man
but for you
I was about it
because it's not tangible you know
I know maybe it doesn't make much sense to you
but don't have to do
have to do it for me
I'm taking a new direction from now on
the most important thing is that I'm much
with my decision man
that's what matters
I spent ninety days thinking I needed
set up a traditional business
to fit in the opinion of others you know
that's when I broke free
and realized i don't need this bro
that the business is here
and then i found out that the business is me man
haha
opa beauty
thanks bro
with god there
how do you
explains that your business is your profession
that your office
is this backpack and that your seat is really the world man
ah doidão
you do not explain
you accept
and then yes you live
and when you break free
you are ready to build your own box
song